<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InfoMate</string>
    <string name="AppDescription"><![CDATA[Your Personal Virtual Guide for Museums & Historical Places]]></string>
    <string name="introduction">Hi there !, I am Infomate. To get started, please turn on NFC functionality of your device and put your device near the Scan here sign</string>
    <string name="Sigiriya"><![CDATA[Sigiriya or Sinhagiri is an ancient rock fortress located in the northern Matale
    District near the town of Dambulla in the Central Province, Sri Lanka.
    \n\n
    The name refers to a site of historical and archaeological significance that is dominated by a massive column of rock around 180 metres (590 ft) high.
    According to the ancient Sri Lankan chronicle the Culavamsa, this site was selected by King Kashyapa (477 – 495 AD) for his new capital.
    \n\n
    He built his palace on the top of this rock and decorated its sides with colourful frescoes.
    On a small plateau about halfway up the side of this rock he built a gateway in the form of an enormous lion.
    ]]></string>
    <string name="NABridge"><![CDATA[The Nine Arch Bridge also called the Bridge in the Sky, is a viaduct bridge in Sri Lanka.
    It is one of the best examples of colonial-era railway construction in the country.
    The construction of the bridge is generally attributed to a local Ceylonese builder, P. K. Appuhami, in consultation with British engineers.
    The chief designer and project manager of the upcountry railway line of Ceylon project was D. J. Wimalasurendra,
    a distinguished Ceylonese engineer and inventor. The designer of the viaduct was Harold Cuthbert Marwood of
    Railway Construction Department of Ceylon Government Railway. The 1923 report titled "Construction of a Concrete Railway Viaduct in Ceylon"
    published by the Engineering Association of Ceylon has details of all the records including the plans and drawings.]]></string>
    <string name="TempleOfTooth"><![CDATA[Temple of the Sacred Tooth Relic commonly known as the
     ශ්‍රී දළදා මාළිගාව (Glorious Tooth Temple), is a Buddhist temple in Kandy, Sri Lanka.
     It is located in the royal palace complex of the former Kingdom of Kandy,
     which houses the relic of the tooth of the Buddha. Since ancient times,
     the relic has played an important role in local politics because it is believed that
     whoever holds the relic holds the governance of the country. The relic was historically held by Sinhalese kings.
     The temple of the tooth is a World Heritage Site mainly due to the temple and the relic.
    ]]></string>
</resources>